

JAYME SUTTON

Healthcare Informatics + UX/UI Developer

PROFILE

I specialize in creating usable digital products that help others feel included and valued. Accomplished health informatics and user researcher with a deep understanding of medical operations, workflows, and revenue cycle operations. Passionate about healthcare technology and services designed with a people-centered approach.

SKILLS

User Research
Information Architecture
Prototyping
Project Management
User Testing
Policy and Procedure Development
Medical Terminology
Legal Compliance
Low to High Fidelity Wireframing
Storyboards
Agile Methodology
Qualitative and Quantitative Research

TOOLBOX

FIGMA
AXURE
ADOBE XD
MIRO
CANVA
MICROSOFT OFFICE
INVISION
BASIC CSS & HTML

MEDICAL SOFTWARE

Modernizing Medicine
Advanced MD
Practice Fusion
Citrix
TheraBill
WebPT
MediSoft
Precision Practice Management
Encoda

CONTACT

Phone

703-772-2186

Email

jaymehendry@outlook.com

Portfolio

https://uxfol.io/733d7bc6

EDUCATION

UX/UI Developer Certification

George Washington University - Washington, DC

September 2022 to February 2023

Master of Business Administration

University of Maryland - Adelphi, MD

January 2022 to Present

Bachelor of Science in Information Systems Management

University of Maryland - Adelphi, MD

August 2019 to August 2021

Associate of Science in Information Technology

Northern Virginia Community College - Arlington, VA

August 2016 to May 2018

EXPERIENCE

Manager, Health Informatics and Revenue Analyst (Remote)

Maryland Vision Center - Frederick, MD (July 2021 to Present)

- Utilizing user experience research to identify and implement quality improvement initiatives geared toward improved client satisfaction.
- Day-to-day planning, oversight, and maintenance of Billing and Revenue Cycle workflow to achieve efficient and effective processes.
- Data-driven guidance to identify and communicate changes in the regulatory environment and trends in the market.
- Implemented and maintained an electronic billing system.
- Create and update practice documents based on changing policy.

Revenue Cycle Analyst

Orthopedic Billing Consultants - Rockville, MD (June 2020 to July 2021)

- Responsible for physician billing, collection, and resolution of insurance processing errors and denials/ appeals.
- The primary responsibilities include working with payers to resolve issues and facilitating prompt claims payment based on knowledge, and understanding of patient billing claims submission, and payerspecific requirements.

Health Informatics Specialist

Bodies in Motion Physical Therapy - Falls Church, VA (June 2014 to June 2020)

- Developed and maintained thorough knowledge of regulatory, departmental, and company policies.
- Auditing paperwork such as applications and licensing documentation for accuracy and ensuring new and current provider enrollment is maintained consistent with all network contracting.
- Liaised with patients, insurance companies, and billing personnel to create and post bills, obtain payments and update the coding system.